Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files J
    - Jarvis, Edward (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 79)
      Photographer if identified: Harold T. Cooper, Wilson, Nichols
    - Jarvis, Herman (Box A-64, Folder 80)
    - Jarvis, Homoselle R. (Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 81)
    - Jarvis, Howard (Box A-64, Folder 82)
    - Jarvis, Idelle Dixon (Box A-64, Folder 83)
    - Jarvis, James (Box A-64, Folder 84)
    - Jarvis, James H. (Box A-64, Folder 85)
    - Jarvis, Kim (Box A-64, Folder 86)
      Photographer if identified: Ricardo Weeks
    - Jarvis, Lucille (Box A-64, Folder 87)
    - Jarvis, William L. (Box A-64, Folder 88)
    - Jasper, Gloria and Jerome (Box A-64, Folder 89)
    - Jasper, Howard D. (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 90)
    - Jasper, Richard (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 91)
    - Jaty, Ra (Box A-64, Folder 92)
    - Javdon, Edward (Deacon) (Box A-64, Folder 93)
    - Javis, Moses (Box A-64, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Heards Studio
    - Javits, Jacob K. (and Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 95)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. Approximately nine prints have single-leaf typescript or carbon typescript leaves attached with staples or adhered to verso with tape.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Nichols, Cecil Layne, Big M, Dummett, Negro Press Photo Service Inc., Wagner International Photos, Ace Creative Photos, Hale Haberman, Leroy Henderson, Eli Aron, Monroe S. Frederick II, Al Levine/Delmonico's Hotel, Jules Schick
    - Javits, Jacob K. (and Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 96)
    - Javits, Marion (Box A-64, Folder 97)
    - Jawara, Dawda, K. (Sir) (Box A-64, Folder 98)
    - Jay, Bobby (Box A-64, Folder 99)
    - Jay, Clair (Box A-64, Folder 100)
      Photographer if identified: Ivan Black Associates, Amsterdam Studios
    - Jay, Claude (Box A-64, Folder 101)
    - Jay, Lillian (Box A-64, Folder 102)
    - Jay, Lillian (Box A-64, Folder 103)
    - "Jaycees" (Box A-64, Folder 104)
      Also one typescript release from Project Mainstream on four leaves, attached with paperclip to one print.
    - Jay-De Merritt Quintet (Box A-64, Folder 105)
    - Jay and the Techniques (Box A-64, Folder 106)
      Also one typescript release on three leaves.
    - Jay, William (Box A-64, Folder 107)
    - Jay, Willie (Box A-64, Folder 108)
      Includes one cut-out piece of a black and white Polaroid print mounted on heavy board.
    - Jaye, Bea (Box A-64, Folder 109)
    - Jaye, L. Errol (Box A-64, Folder 110)
    - Jaye, Miles (Box A-64, Folder 111)
    - Jazz (Box A-64, Folder 112)
      Includes one architectural rendering of The Jazz Cultural Center printed on RC paper. Also two velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos, TWA/John F. Kennedy International Airport
    - Jazzie B (Box A-64, Folder 113)
    - Jazzmobile (Box A-64, Folder 114)
    - Jean-Gilles, Brunet (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 115)
    - Jean, Gloria (Box A-64, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: Ray Jones
    - Jean-Louis, Suelva L. and Butler (Box A-64, Folder 117)
    - Jeannette, Gertrude (Box A-64, Folder 118)
    - Jean-Pierre, W.A. (Box A-64, Folder 119)
    - Jeans, Robert L. (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: The Scurlock Studios
    - Jeanty, Constant (Box A-64, Folder 121)
    - Jeff, Kevin (Box A-64, Folder 122)
    - Jeff, Waldo (Box A-64, Folder 123)
    - Jeffe, Sam (Box A-64, Folder 124)
    - Jefferies, Edward D. (Box A-64, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: Frank E. Edwards Jr.
    - Jefferies, Fran (Box A-64, Folder 126)
    - Jefferies, James J. (Box A-64, Folder 127)
    - Jefferies, Victoria B. (Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 128)
    - Jeffers, Audrey (Hon.) (Box A-64, Folder 129)
    - Jeffers, Grady R. (Box A-64, Folder 130)
      Photographer if identified: Lew Merrim
    - Jeffers, Gwen (Box A-64, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: D. Mahon
    - Jeffers, James T. (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 132)
    - Jeffers, Janice (Box A-64, Folder 133)
    - Jeffers, Leroy (Box A-64, Folder 134)
    - Jefferson, Alicia (Box A-64, Folder 135)
    - Jefferson, Ann (Box A-64, Folder 136)
    - Jefferson, Anna V. (Sen.) (Box A-64, Folder 137)
    - Jefferson, Bill (Box A-64, Folder 138)
    - Jefferson, Bobbi (Box A-64, Folder 139)
    - Jefferson, Clive (Box A-64, Folder 140)
    - Jefferson, Clyde (Bishop) (Box A-64, Folder 141)
      One newspaper clipping.
    - Jefferson, Delaware (Box A-64, Folder 142)
    - Jefferson, Elizabeth (Box A-64, Folder 143)
    - Jefferson, Elwood C. (Box A-64, Folder 144)
    - Jefferson (Endorses) (Box A-64, Folder 145)
    - Jefferson, Eva (Box A-64, Folder 146)
    - Jefferson, Floyd (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 147)
    - Jefferson, Gary (Box A-64, Folder 148)
    - Jefferson, George and Prentiss (Box A-64, Folder 149)
    - Jefferson, Ioneze (Box A-64, Folder 150)
    - Jefferson, John (Box A-64, Folder 151)
    - Jefferson, Karen (Box A-64, Folder 152)
    - Jefferson, Louise (artist) (Box A-64, Folder 153)
      Includes one black and white Polaroid print.
      Photographer if identified: Louise E. Jefferson
    - Jefferson, Luke (Box A-64, Folder 154)
    - Jefferson, Mark (Box A-64, Folder 155)
    - Jefferson, Mary (Box A-64, Folder 156)
    - Jefferson, Mildred (Box A-64, Folder 157)
      With ink ms. note to editor on the image recto.
    - Jefferson, Patricia (Box A-64, Folder 158)
    - Jefferson, Richard (Box A-64, Folder 159)
    - Jefferson, Robert (Box A-64, Folder 160)
      Includes two RC paper reproductions of illustrated Jack and Jill Magazine covers.
    - Jefferson, Roland S., M.D. (Box A-64, Folder 161)
    - Jefferson, Rosetta (Box A-64, Folder 162)
    - Jefferson, Roy (Box A-64, Folder 163)
    - Jefferson, Sam (Box A-64, Folder 164)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Box A-64, Folder 165)
    - Jefferson, Thomas K. (Box A-64, Folder 166)
    - "The Jeffersons" (Box A-64, Folder 167)
    - Jeffrey, Albert (Box A-64, Folder 168)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Metropolitan Photo Service Inc.
    - Jeffries, Ira L. (Box A-64, Folder 169)
    - Jeffries, J.B. (Box A-64, Folder 170)
      Also one strip of black and white 6"x6" negatives, two frames, in an envelope.
      Photographer if identified: Morgan Gwenwald, Dummett
    - Jeffries, Clinton (Box A-64, Folder 171)
    - Jeffries, Ethel (Box A-64, Folder 172)
    - Jeffries, Fred R. (Box A-64, Folder 173)
    - Jeffries, Herb (Box A-64, Folder 174)
    - Jeffries, Joseph (Box A-64, Folder 175)
    - Jeffries, Leonard (velox) (Box A-64, Folder 176)
    - Jeffries, Leonard (velox) (Box A-64, Folder 177)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore
    - Jeffries, Leonard (protesters - American Conservative Alliance) (Box A-64, Folder 178)
    - Jeffries, LeRoy W. (Box A-64, Folder 179)
      Also one typescript release on two leaves, stapled to border of print.
    - Jeffries, Onde H. (Box A-64, Folder 180)
    - Jeffries, Rosalyn Robinson (Box A-64, Folder 181)
    - Jeffries, Sandra (Box A-64, Folder 182)
    - Jeffries, Thomas (Box A-64, Folder 183)
    - Jeffries, Marland (Box A-64, Folder 184)
    - Jeffries, Varbara (Box A-64, Folder 185)
    - Jehovah's Witnesses (Box A-64, Folder 186)
    - Jejada, Charles (Box A-64, Folder 187)
    - Jemiekay, King (Box A-64, Folder 188)
    - Jemison, Mae (Box A-64, Folder 189)
    - Jemison, Robert L. (Box A-64, Folder 190)
      Photographer if identified: H.A. Phan Stiller/U.S. Navy
    - Jemison, Theodore (Box A-64, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Lensman
    - Jemmott, Jerry (Box A-64, Folder 192)
    - Jenkins, Albin "Humpty" (Box A-64, Folder 193)
    - Jenkins, Alice (Box A-64, Folder 194)
    - Jenkins, Allen (Box A-64, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Army/Eastern Area/Military Traffic Management and Terminal Service
    - Jenkins, Andrew (Box A-64, Folder 196)
    - Jenkins, Anthony Fisher (Box A-64, Folder 197)
    - Jenkins, Augustus (Box A-64, Folder 198)
    - Jenkins, Ayodele (Box A-64, Folder 199)
    - Jenkins, Benyomen (Box A-64, Folder 200)
    - Jenkins, Carey (Box A-64, Folder 201)
    - Jenkins, Carol Ann (Box A-64, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Harris Photo, Wagner International Photos, Pictorial Enterprise, Frederick La-Mar Associates, Norman Frederick, Bill Price, Bob Head, Raimondo Borea
    - Jenkins, Carey (Box A-64, Folder 203)
    - Jenkins, Charles (Box A-64, Folder 204)
    - Jenkins, Christopher (Box A-64, Folder 205)
    - Jenkins, Clifford (Box A-64, Folder 206)
    - Jenkins, Cornelius (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 207)
    - Jenkins, Connie (Box A-64, Folder 208)
    - Jenkins, Donald (Box A-64, Folder 209)
      Photographer if identified: Esopus Prep School
    - Jenkins, Cynthia (Box A-64, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Jenkins, Edwin G. (Box A-64, Folder 211)
    - Jenkins, Doris (Box A-64, Folder 212)
    - Jenkins, Elizabeth G. (Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 213)
    - Jenkins, Emmanuel L. (Commander) (Box A-64, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: United States Merchant Marine Academy
    - Jenkins, Ethel (Box A-64, Folder 215)
      Photographer if identified: Star Journal, American Cancer Society
    - Jenkins, Ferguson (Box A-64, Folder 216)
    - Jenkins, Freddie (Box A-64, Folder 217)
    - Jenkins, Frederick (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 218)
      Photographer if identified: Art Photo Studio
    - Jenkins, Garlien (Box A-64, Folder 219)
    - Jenkins, Gwen (Box A-64, Folder 220)
    - Jenkins, Harriet (Box A-64, Folder 221)
    - Jenkins, Harold A. (Box A-64, Folder 222)
    - Jenkins, Helen (Box A-64, Folder 223)
      Photographer if identified: Long Island Educational Television Council Inc.
    - Jenkins, Helene (Box A-64, Folder 224)
    - Jenkins, Harriet G. (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 225)
    - Jenkins, Howard (Box A-64, Folder 226)
      Also one print on lightweight acidic paper that is badly darkened and has stained the surrounding prints and folder.
    - Jenkins, J. Dallas (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 227)
      Also one velox. Also one release on two typescript leaves, stapled through one small print.
    - Jenkins, Jake (Box A-64, Folder 228)
    - Jenkins, James (Box A-64, Folder 229)
    - Jenkins, Jim (Box A-64, Folder 230)
    - Jenkins, Joe (Box A-64, Folder 231)
    - Jenkins, John (Dr. and Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 232)
    - Jenkins, John, Jr. (Box A-64, Folder 233)
    - Jenkins, John L. (Box A-64, Folder 234)
    - Jenkins, Joseph D. (Box A-64, Folder 235)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Camera Arts Studio
    - Jenkins, Joseph E. (Box A-64, Folder 236)
    - Jenkins, Joseph (Patrolman) (Box A-64, Folder 237)
    - Jenkins, Joyce (Box A-64, Folder 238)
    - Jenkins, Joseph W. (Box A-64, Folder 239)
    - Jenkins, Kenneth (Box A-64, Folder 240)
    - Jenkins, Lee (Box A-64, Folder 241)
    - Jenkins, Lenore (Box A-64, Folder 242)
    - Jenkins, Leroy (Box A-64, Folder 243)
    - Jenkins, Lillette Harris (Box A-64, Folder 244)
    - Jenkins, Linzo (Box A-64, Folder 245)
    - Jenkins, Lloyd (Box A-64, Folder 246)
    - Jenkins, Loreen (Box A-64, Folder 247)
    - Jenkins, Lyn (Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 248)
    - Jenkins, Mamie (Box A-64, Folder 249)
    - Jenkins, Margaret, Dance Studio (Box A-64, Folder 250)
    - Jenkins, Martin D. (Box A-64, Folder 251)
      Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach, Herbert Hawkins
    - Henkins, Matilda (Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 252)
    - Jenkins, Melvin E. (Box A-64, Folder 253)
    - Jenkins, Mildred (Box A-64, Folder 254)
    - Jenkins, Monroe (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-64, Folder 255)
    - Jenkins, Muriel E. (Box A-64, Folder 256)
      Photographer if identified: The Bing Studio
    - Jenkins, Natalie (Box A-64, Folder 257)
    - Jenkins, Norman (Mrs. and Daughter) (Box A-64, Folder 258)
    - Jenkins, Ora Leo (Box A-64, Folder 259)
    - Jenkins, Paula Louise (Box A-64, Folder 260)
    - Jenkins, "Pee Wee" (Box A-64, Folder 261)
    - Jenkins, Philip M. (Box A-64, Folder 262)
      Photographer if identified: John R. Brooks Jr.
    - Jenkins, Ralph (Box A-64, Folder 263)
    - Jenkins, Ray (Box A-64, Folder 264)
    - Jenkins, Raymond P. (Box A-64, Folder 265)
      Photographer if identified: Winburn
    - Jenkins, Sam (Box A-64, Folder 266)
    - Jenkins, Samuel E. (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 267)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, George Maniatis
    - Jenkins, Samuel F. (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 268)
    - Jenkins, Sara (Box A-64, Folder 269)
    - Jenkins, Shirley (Box A-64, Folder 270)
      Photographer if identified: Housing and Development Administration, N.Y.C. Housing Authority, Harris Photo
    - Jenkins, Timothy (Box A-64, Folder 271)
    - Jenkins, Timothy L. (Box A-64, Folder 272)
    - Jenkins, Thelma (Box A-64, Folder 273)
      Showing 25th Anniversary party at Amsterdam News.
    - Jenkins, Thomas E. (Box A-64, Folder 274)
    - Jenkins, Tommy (Box A-64, Folder 275)
    - Jenkins, Veronica (Box A-64, Folder 276)
    - Jenkins, Vivian (Rev.) (Box A-64, Folder 277)
    - Jenkins, Vivian Brown (Box A-64, Folder 278)
    - Jenkins, Wayne (Box A-64, Folder 279)
    - Jenkins, William (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 280)
    - Jenkins, William E. (Box A-64, Folder 281)
    - Jenkins, William P. (Box A-64, Folder 282)
      Photographer if identified: W.L. Grant
    - Jenkins, Willie (Box A-64, Folder 283)
      Typescript press release (4 p.), affixed to print with tape
    - Jennett, Violet E. (Box A-64, Folder 284)
      Photographer if identified: Photo Communications Co. Inc.
    - Jennings, Alvin (Box A-64, Folder 285)
    - Jennings, Arnita (Box A-64, Folder 286)
    - Jennings, Benjamin (Box A-64, Folder 287)
    - Jennings, Bill E. (Box A-64, Folder 288)
    - Jennings, Charles S. (Box A-64, Folder 289)
    - Jennings, Irving (Box A-64, Folder 290)
    - Jennings, Isabel (Miss) (Box A-64, Folder 291)
    - Jennings, James (Dr.) (Box A-64, Folder 292)
    - Jennings, Karen (Box A-64, Folder 293)
    - Jennings, Leroy (Box A-64, Folder 294)
    - Jones, Wiletha (Box A-64, Folder 295)
    - Jennings, Marilyn (Box A-65, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Shelley Brown, Harris Photo
    - Jennings, Nathan (Box A-65, Folder 2)
    - Jennings, Robert (Box A-65, Folder 3)
    - Jennings, Sammy (Box A-65, Folder 4)
      One print has a typescript leaf affixed to the recto with a paper clip.
      Photographer if identified: Arsene Studio
    - Jennings, Waylon (Box A-65, Folder 5)
      Press release affixed to verso.
    - Jennings, William E (Box A-65, Folder 6)
    - Jenny's Daughters (Box A-65, Folder 7)
      One print has two photocopies of press release affixed with a paper clip. Also one velox print.
    - Jensen, Hilmar L., Jr. (Box A-65, Folder 8)
    - Jeppe, Miriam & Melissa (Box A-65, Folder 9)
    - Jepperson, Jewel (Box A-65, Folder 10)
      photocopied press release affixed to recto with staple.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Keno
    - Jergason, Gutchen (Box A-65, Folder 11)
    - Jerico Jim Crow (Box A-65, Folder 12)
    - Jernagin, W. H. (Dr.) (Box A-65, Folder 13)
      Two prints with carbonscript leaves affixed to verso; one with typescript leaf affixed to verso. Also 3 paper stereotype matrices; one newspaper clipping.
      Photographer if identified: Fred Hess & Son, Pat Alves, Scurlock Studio
    - Jerraids, Crystal (Box A-65, Folder 14)
    - Jerry, Bruno (Box A-65, Folder 15)
    - Jerry, Cynthia (Box A-65, Folder 16)
      Press release affixed with a paper clip.
    - Jerry, Minnie (Box A-65, Folder 17)
    - Jervis, Enid L. (Box A-65, Folder 18)
    - Jessamy, Howard (Box A-65, Folder 19)
    - Jessamy, Kenneth A. (Box A-65, Folder 20)
    - Jessamy, Ronald (Box A-65, Folder 21)
    - Jesse, James and Cornell (Box A-65, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: Diaz & Rogers
    - Jessie, Wayman (Box A-65, Folder 23)
    - Jessmey, Willie (Box A-65, Folder 24)
      Note on folder: "see Jackson, Levine."
    - Jessye, Eva (& choir members) (Box A-65, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Continental News Photo
    - Jesus Christ (Box A-65, Folder 26)
    - Jesus Christ Supestar (Box A-65, Folder 27)
      With a press release attached with a paper clip.
    - Jet Set (Box A-65, Folder 28)
    - Jet Sweepstakes Winner (Box A-65, Folder 29)
    - Jeter, Bertha M. (Box A-65, Folder 30)
      Print is pasted to a blank leaf.
    - Jeter, Dorothy (Box A-65, Folder 31)
    - Jeter, James (Box A-65, Folder 32)
    - Jeter, James P., Jr. ( Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 33)
    - Jeter, Mable (Box A-65, Folder 34)
    - Jeter, Shirley A. (Box A-65, Folder 35)
    - Jeter, Sinclair Henry (Box A-65, Folder 36)
    - Jethroe, Sammy (Box A-65, Folder 37)
    - Jett, Eola (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 38)
    - Jett, Evangeline A. (Box A-65, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Lewis Studios
    - Jett, Ruth (Box A-65, Folder 40)
    - Jett, Sandra (Box A-65, Folder 41)
    - Jetter, Theresa (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 42)
    - Jetter, Watts (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 43)
      Myrna Loy and Mrs. Count Basie also in picture.
    - Jewel, Bishop M. L. (Box A-65, Folder 44)
    - Jewel Box Review (Box A-65, Folder 45)
    - Jewel Restaurant (Box A-65, Folder 46)
    - Jewell, Aander (Box A-65, Folder 47)
    - Jewell, Paula (Box A-65, Folder 48)
    - Jewels (Box A-65, Folder 49)
    - Jewels, The (Box A-65, Folder 50)
    - Jewett, Morine (Box A-65, Folder 51)
    - Jews (Box A-65, Folder 52)
    - Jewish Museum of New York (Box A-65, Folder 53)
    - Jive Five, The (Box A-65, Folder 54)
    - Jiggetts, Bess (Box A-65, Folder 55)
    - Jiggetts, J. Ida (Box A-65, Folder 56)
    - Jiggetts, J. Ida (Box A-65, Folder 57)
      One print has ms. biography on verso and typescript transcription of same attached with paper clip; small ms. note.
      Photographer if identified: Bing Studio, Roberts Photo Studio, Cecil Layne, Rumar Studio
    - Jiggetts, J. Philip (Box A-65, Folder 58)
    - Jiggetts, Roberts (Dr.) (Box A-65, Folder 59)
    - Jii, Dottie (Box A-65, Folder 60)
    - Jiles, M. (Box A-65, Folder 61)
    - Jiles, William J. (Rev.) (Box A-65, Folder 62)
    - Jimenez (Box A-65, Folder 63)
    - Jimenez, Marilyn (Box A-65, Folder 64)
    - Jimeniz, Ramon (Box A-65, Folder 65)
    - Jimmy & Vella (Box A-65, Folder 66)
    - Jimmy Butts Trio (Box A-65, Folder 67)
    - Jimmy Castor Quartet, The (Box A-65, Folder 68)
    - Jo, Damita (Box A-65, Folder 69)
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams, TWA
    - Joahanne (Box A-65, Folder 70)
      Also in folder: a print of Dr. Yosef Ben-Jochannon.
    - Jochannon, Yosef Ben- (Dr.) (Box A-65, Folder 70)
      Located in folder titled "Joahanne."
    - Jo-Ann, Ebony (Box A-65, Folder 71)
      One has photocopy biography stapled to print
      Photographer if identified: Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, Hakim
    - Joans, Ted (Box A-65, Folder 72)
      Photographer if identified: Paula Court, Marion Kalter
    - Joardan, Roy (Box A-65, Folder 73)
    - Job Corps (Box A-65, Folder 74)
      One print has caption on letterhead attached with paper clip; one has photocopy press release attached to print with staples
    - Jobettes (Box A-65, Folder 75)
    - Jockanoo (Box A-65, Folder 76)
    - Jockier, James (Box A-65, Folder 77)
    - Jocko (Box A-65, Folder 78)
      Note on folder: "Douglas Wellington Henderson, Dr."
    - Joda, Adetuuji (Box A-65, Folder 79)
    - Joe & Eddie (Box A-65, Folder 80)
    - Joe, Billy (Box A-65, Folder 81)
    - Joe, Montego (Box A-65, Folder 82)
    - Joe, Syd (Box A-65, Folder 83)
    - Joel, Buelah (Box A-65, Folder 84)
    - Joel, Lawrence (Box A-65, Folder 85)
    - Joel, Leonal (Box A-65, Folder 86)
    - Joffrey Ballet (Box A-65, Folder 87)
      With photocopied press release.
    - Johari, Azizi (Box A-65, Folder 88)
    - John, Curtis (Box A-65, Folder 89)
    - John, Alma Vessel (Box A-65, Folder 90)
      Also 5 velox prints and one photocopied press release.
      Photographer if identified: Ronnie Brathwaite, George Frye, Harris Photo, Bill Carter, Bert Andrews, Board of Education, Frederick's Pictorial Service, A. Hansen
    - John, Alma Vessel (Box A-65, Folder 91)
      Also one velox print. Typescript press release attached to group of prints by paper clip
      Photographer if identified: M Associates, Raymond Borea, Bob Head, Pictorial Enterprise, Peter Moran
    - John, Dewitt (Box A-65, Folder 92)
    - John, Dorothy Little (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 93)
    - John, Easterline (Box A-65, Folder 94)
    - John, Elton (Box A-65, Folder 95)
    - John, Errol (Box A-65, Folder 96)
    - John, Floral (Box A-65, Folder 97)
    - John, Ivan B. (Box A-65, Folder 98)
    - John, Linda (Box A-65, Folder 99)
    - John, Mable (Box A-65, Folder 100)
    - John, Russell (Box A-65, Folder 101)
    - John's Bargain Stores Scholarship Awards (Box A-65, Folder 102)
    - Johnathan, Diane (Box A-65, Folder 103)
    - Johniken, Winona (Box A-65, Folder 104)
      Note on folder: "see Miss Carroll 1966"
    - Johnnie & Joe (Box A-65, Folder 105)
      Two-leaf press release/bio attached to print with paper clip.
    - Johnny K (Box A-65, Folder 106)
    - Johns, Agnes (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 107)
    - Johns, Bernard (Box A-65, Folder 108)
    - Johns, Burton K. (Box A-65, Folder 109)
    - Johns, Cleo (Box A-65, Folder 110)
    - Johns, Constance (Box A-65, Folder 111)
    - Johns, Denise (Box A-65, Folder 112)
    - Johns, Willie (Box A-65, Folder 113)
    - Johnson, A.J. (Box A-65, Folder 114)
    - Johnson, Abraham (Capt.) (Box A-65, Folder 115)
      Photographer if identified: Hastings-Willinger & Associates
    - Johnson, Adell (rev.) (Box A-65, Folder 116)
    - Johnson, Adrian (Box A-65, Folder 117)
    - Johnson, Adrianis (Box A-65, Folder 118)
    - Johnson, Al (Box A-65, Folder 119)
    - Johnson, Albert E. (Box A-65, Folder 120)
    - Johnson, Albert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 121)
    - Johnson, Albert T. (Box A-65, Folder 122)
      Newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Platnick Photos
    - Johnson, Alfred I. (Box A-65, Folder 123)
    - Johnson, Alice (Box A-65, Folder 124)
    - Johnson, Alma (Box A-65, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: Baskerville
    - Johnson, Alvin (Box A-65, Folder 126)
    - Johnson, Alvin D. (Box A-65, Folder 127)
    - Johnson, Andrew L. (Rev.) (Box A-65, Folder 128)
    - Johnson, Angela (Box A-65, Folder 129)
    - Johnson, Anita B. (Box A-65, Folder 130)
    - Johnson, Anthony (Box A-65, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: M Asscociates
    - Johnson, Arnold (Box A-65, Folder 132)
      Also one contact sheet image and an ms. phone message note.
    - Johnson, Arnold P. (Box A-65, Folder 133)
    - Johnson, Arthur (Box A-65, Folder 134)
    - Johnson, Arzie R. (Box A-65, Folder 135)
    - Johnson, Asaponsa (Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 136)
      Label on folder: "Johnson, Asa John."
    - Johnson, Asaponsa (Rev.) (Box A-65, Folder 137)
    - Johnson, Audrey (Box A-65, Folder 138)
    - Johnson, Audrey W. (Box A-65, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: Vernon L. Smith
    - Johnson, Barbara (Box A-65, Folder 140)
    - Johnson, Basil (Box A-65, Folder 141)
    - Johnson, Benjamin (Box A-65, Folder 142)
      photocopied press release affixed to print with staple.
    - Johnson, M. Bernadine (Box A-65, Folder 143)
    - Johnson, Bernard (Box A-65, Folder 144)
    - Johnson, Bernard (Box A-65, Folder 145)
    - Johnson, Bernard (Box A-65, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Michael Alexander
    - Johnson, Bernard (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-65, Folder 147)
    - Johnson, Bernice (Box A-65, Folder 148)